<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Yulu (Laura) Lin</title><link>https://laura-lin.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Yulu (Laura) Lin</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 15:56:43 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://laura-lin.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Autonomous vehicles and visually impaired people's interaction</title><link>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/av-vision/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 15:56:43 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/av-vision/</guid><description>Human machine interaction This project is an ongoing work about visually impaired people and autonomous vehicles' interaction. Researchers want to know how can visually impaired people need when they use autonomous vehicles in the future.
Problem statement Alhough there are several methods for visually impaired people to get help from the society, they still facing increasing difficulities when taking mobility tools like public transportation, Uber/Lyft or taxises. Orientation &amp;amp; Mobility (O&amp;amp;M) has been developed for 2 decades, and many people have been trained to help visually impaired and blind people&amp;rsquo;s mobility, however, blind and visually impaired people&amp;rsquo;s mental health and their dependent mobility have become a series problem.</description></item><item><title>Mindful people's preferences on autonomous vehicles</title><link>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/mindfulav/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 15:44:46 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/mindfulav/</guid><description>I did the project when I was a Research Assistant at Haved university, Langer Lab (Advised by Prof.Ellen Langer). Two publications of the project have been accepted by VEHITS2021 and SoCAV2021.
The keywords include: Autonomous Vehicles, Travel Behavior, Travel Costs, Trust, Income, Open to Change, Policy, Design.
Most important concepts of the research projects: Mindfulness
People absorb information more or less mindfully, much the same way as they act with differing degrees of self-reflection.</description></item><item><title>People's Preferences for Different Uses of Autonomous Vehicles in China</title><link>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/mindful-avch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 15:56:43 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/mindful-avch/</guid><description>Problem Statement People in China want to use autonomous vehicles, but restricted by color, price, type and different uses, we are still unclear about their preferences on autonomous vehicles. Such preferences generate those questions:
What kind of autonomous vehicles do people in the metropolitan areas like mostly in China? What price will people accept when considering owning an autonomous vehicle or subscribe autonomous vehicles as long-term owner? What different uses do people prefer when using autonomous vehicles?</description></item><item><title>Mindful people's preferences on autonomous vehicles</title><link>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/x/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/x/</guid><description>Most important concepts of the research projects: Mindfulness
People absorb information more or less mindfully, much the same way as they act with differing degrees of self-reflection. Too often, individuals seize on standard classifications, use routine rules and procedures, and then proceed to become seduced by habits (Wayne et al., 2006).
Autonomomous vehicles
In recent years, many manufacturers and software companies announced that autonomous vehicles will be in the market shortly (Menno et al.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/bviav/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://laura-lin.github.io/portfolio/bviav/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>