<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My New Hugo Site</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 15:56:43 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Autonomous vehicles and visually impaired people's interaction</title><link>http://example.org/portfolio/av-vision/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 15:56:43 +0600</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/portfolio/av-vision/</guid><description>Human machine interaction This project is an ongoing work about visually impaired people and autonomous vehicles' interaction. Researchers want to know how can visually impaired people need when they use autonomous vehicles in the future.
Problem statement Alhough there are several methods for visually impaired people to get help from the society, they still facing increasing difficulities when taking mobility tools like public transportation, Uber/Lyft or taxises. Orientation &amp;amp; Mobility (O&amp;amp;M) has been developed for 2 decades, and many people have been trained to help visually impaired and blind people&amp;rsquo;s mobility, however, blind and visually impaired people&amp;rsquo;s mental health and their dependent mobility have become a series problem.</description></item><item><title>Mindful people's preferences on autonomous vehicles</title><link>http://example.org/portfolio/mindfulav/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 15:44:46 +0600</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/portfolio/mindfulav/</guid><description>I did the project when I was a Research Assistant at Haved university, Langer Lab (Advised by Prof.Ellen Langer). Two publications of the project have been accepted by VEHITS2021 and SoCAV2021.
The keywords include: Autonomous Vehicles, Travel Behavior, Travel Costs, Trust, Income, Open to Change, Policy, Design.
Most important concepts of the research projects: Mindfulness
People absorb information more or less mindfully, much the same way as they act with differing degrees of self-reflection.</description></item><item><title>Mindful People's Preference for Different Services of Autonomous Vehicles in China</title><link>http://example.org/blog/mindfulav/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 13:36:06 +0600</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/mindfulav/</guid><description>Abstract: This paper draws from people’s choices of different services in autonomous vehicles to generate new insights about their acceptance of autonomous vehicles to meet their mobility needs. This article highlights the relationship between people’s mindfulness and their choice of the following applications of autonomous driving technology: self-driving-uber, car-sharing (Car2go), subway/rail, rental car, paratransit, self-owned autonomous car, self-driving car subscription, and self-driving bus. A quantitative analysis shows that in Chinese metropolitan areas, mindful people’s trust, health situations, travel costs, knowledge of autonomous vehicles, and their willingness to change their travel mode are significantly related to their choosing autonomous paratransit as their preferred mode.</description></item><item><title>People's Preferences for Different Uses of Autonomous Vehicles in China</title><link>http://example.org/portfolio/mindful-avch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 15:56:43 +0600</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/portfolio/mindful-avch/</guid><description>Problem Statement People in China want to use autonomous vehicles, but restricted by color, price, type and different uses, we are still unclear about their preferences on autonomous vehicles. Such preferences generate those questions:
What kind of autonomous vehicles do people in the metropolitan areas like mostly in China? What price will people accept when considering owning an autonomous vehicle or subscribe autonomous vehicles as long-term owner? What different uses do people prefer when using autonomous vehicles?</description></item><item><title>People’s Preferences for Different Uses of Autonomous Vehicles in China</title><link>http://example.org/blog/peoplepreferenceav/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:40:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/peoplepreferenceav/</guid><description>Abstract: people’s mindfulness score, trust, health situations, travel costs, knowledge of autonomous vehicles, and their willingness to change their travel mode are significantly related to their choosing autonomous paratransit as their preferred mode. Policymakers can focus on providing enough information about autonomous vehicles’ prices for people with low income and high travel costs. When design autonomous vehicles, people with high mindfulness level will be more acceptable to paratransit services.
This work was presented in 2021 International Conference on Vehicle Technology and Intelligent Transport Systems (VEHITS) VEHITS 2021.</description></item></channel></rss>