<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Publications and Presentations on My New Hugo Site</title><link>http://example.org/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Publications and Presentations on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 20:17:01 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mindful People's Preference for Different Services of Autonomous Vehicles in China</title><link>http://example.org/blog/mindfulav/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 13:36:06 +0600</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/mindfulav/</guid><description>Abstract: This paper draws from people’s choices of different services in autonomous vehicles to generate new insights about their acceptance of autonomous vehicles to meet their mobility needs. This article highlights the relationship between people’s mindfulness and their choice of the following applications of autonomous driving technology: self-driving-uber, car-sharing (Car2go), subway/rail, rental car, paratransit, self-owned autonomous car, self-driving car subscription, and self-driving bus. A quantitative analysis shows that in Chinese metropolitan areas, mindful people’s trust, health situations, travel costs, knowledge of autonomous vehicles, and their willingness to change their travel mode are significantly related to their choosing autonomous paratransit as their preferred mode.</description></item><item><title>People’s Preferences for Different Uses of Autonomous Vehicles in China</title><link>http://example.org/blog/peoplepreferenceav/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:40:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/peoplepreferenceav/</guid><description>Abstract: people’s mindfulness score, trust, health situations, travel costs, knowledge of autonomous vehicles, and their willingness to change their travel mode are significantly related to their choosing autonomous paratransit as their preferred mode. Policymakers can focus on providing enough information about autonomous vehicles’ prices for people with low income and high travel costs. When design autonomous vehicles, people with high mindfulness level will be more acceptable to paratransit services.
This work was presented in 2021 International Conference on Vehicle Technology and Intelligent Transport Systems (VEHITS) VEHITS 2021.</description></item></channel></rss>